你们好
Hey, you guys.
- 嘿   - 你们在做什么？
- Hey.     - What are you doing?
- 规划我们的婚礼   - 真巧 我们也正在做同一件事
- Figuring out our wedding plans.     - We were doing the same thing.
耶
Yeah.
太疯狂了 会场 礼服 喜宴
It's really crazy. The hall, the dress, the food.
- 我完全不知道会这么贵   - 没错 真的是很贵
- I had no idea how expensive this stuff was.     - Yeah, it is really pricey.
- 当我听到价目时 都快发疯了   - 那你们怎么办？
- I freaked when I heard the numbers.    - So, what did you two do about it?
很简单 我想出一些 削减开支的办法
It was simple. I came up with some cost-cutting solutions...
列了一张清单 然后摩妮卡就叫我去死
...wrote out a list and Monica told me to go to hell.
没有什么解决的办法
There's no way around it.
你只能接受得花大钱的事实
Just accept that this is gonna cost a lot of money.
我听说婚礼的相关产业 一年营业额为四百亿美元
I heard that weddings are, like, a $40 billion-a-year industry.
没错 我大概就贡献了一半
Yeah. And I'm responsible for just, like, half of that.
说真的 这些钱应该有更好的用途
But really, it does seem like this money could be put to better use.
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
是啊 你觉得如果我们 把婚礼的钱捐给慈善机构…
Yeah. Now, how would you feel if we gave all the wedding money to charity...
然后我们在市政府结婚 如何？
...and we just got married at City Hall?
我觉得那样会让我更想娶你
I think it would make me wanna marry you even more.
我得告诉你们 那是绝佳的示爱方式
Well, I gotta say, you guys, that's an incredible gesture.
或许你下次结婚时就可以那么做
Maybe you do that next time you get married.
不…下次要在夏威夷的日落时分
No, no, no. The next time's gonna be Hawaii at sunset.
或许下下一次
But maybe the time after that.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
有什么事吗？
What's going on?
审核我们申请收养的社福人员要来 所以我们在打扫公寓
Our adoption social worker is coming by, so we're cleaning the apartment.
"我们"？
"We"?
你明知你不要我帮忙 你不能脚踏两条船
You know you don't want me to help. You can't have it both ways.
这个人有权决定 你们能不能领养婴儿吗？
Hey, is this the person who decides whether or not you get a baby?
- 她要来看看我们住的地方   - 必须要完美无缺
- Kind of. She's coming to see where we live.     - And it has to go perfectly.
如果她不喜欢我们 她可以不接受我们的美国领养申请
If she doesn't like us, she can keep us off every adoption list in the state.
或许我应该过来露个面 她可能是我的连续剧迷
Hey, maybe I should stop by. She could be a soap-opera fan.
小人物能够认识大明星 会很令人印象深刻的
It's very impressive when the little people know a celebrity.
"小人物"？
"Little people"?
"大明星"
"Celebrity."
我想我整理好这里了
So I think I'm just about done here.
除非你在某处藏了不好的东西 像是色情杂志或香烟？
Unless you have any bad stuff hidden somewhere, like porn or cigarettes?
什么？
What?
- 当然没有   - 钱德
- No.     - Chandler.
我没有藏 而且我被你的影射冒犯了
I don't, and I'm offended by the insinuation.
好 所以沙发底下没有色情杂志
So there's not a magazine under the couch...
马桶水箱后也没有 用胶带黏住的香烟
...or a pack of cigarettes taped to the back of the toilet tank...
或者录影机里的下流录影带？
...or a filthy video in the VCR?
我承认香烟和杂志
I'll admit to the cigarettes and the magazine.
但是录影带不是我的
But that tape is not mine.
- 也不是我的   - 我猜我们永远不会知道是谁的
- It isn't mine.     - I guess we'll never know whose it is.
（纽约市 儿童基金会）
- 有我可以效劳的地方吗？ - 是
- May I help you?     - Yes.
我们是来捐一笔 相当大的款项给小孩们
We're here to make a rather sizable donation to the children.
不论是大或小的捐款 我们都很感激
Well, any contribution, large or small, is appreciated.
我想这笔会让你感激得屁滚尿流
Well, I think you're gonna appreciate the crap out of this one.
- 非常慷慨   - 我们不想被表扬
- Well, this is very generous.     - And we don't want any recognition.
请匿名处理
This is completely anonymous.
匿名处理 来自两位仁慈的陌生人
Completely anonymous. From two kind strangers.
张三先生和菲比布非
Mr. X and Phoebe Buffay.
我们可以把你们的名字 放在我们的刊物上
We can put your names in our newsletter.
- 不需要   - 布非是布料的布 非常的非
- Not necessary.     - Buffay is spelled B-U-F-F-A-Y.
张三是"麦克汉尼根"
And X is spelled, uh, "Mike Hannigan."
我代表孩子们非常感谢两位
All right, well, on behalf of the children, thank you both very much.
- 很高兴我们这么做 感觉真好   - 没错 感觉真好
- Sure. I'm glad we did this. It feels so good.     - It does. It feels really good.
你看 我们得到免费的T恤
Oh, look. And we get these free T-shirts.
其实那是我上健身房穿的
Actually, that's the shirt I wore to the gym.
难怪湿湿的
It's moist.
- 你好 艾玛很快就会醒来的   - 很好
- Emma will be up in a minute.     - Oh, good.
罗斯 我听说了你和查莉的事 我很遗憾
Oh, hey, Ross, listen. I heard about you and Charlie. I'm really sorry.
没关系 我相信 漂亮的古生物学家多的是
Aw, that's okay. I'm sure there are tons of other beautiful paleontologists out there.
- 没错   - 她是绝无仅有的
- Absolutely.     - There was one. She's it.
其他的看起来都像是 应该去住在桥下
All the rest look like they should live under a bridge.
你今天打算要做什么？
So, uh, what are you gonna do today?
我想说带艾玛去游乐场
Well, I was thinking of taking Emma to the playground.
我的天 什么？
Oh, my God. What?
我刚刚说的是 我想带艾玛 去上刀山下油锅博物馆
Like I said, I was thinking of taking Emma to the Museum of Knives and Fire.
听着 罗斯 我不希望艾玛去游乐场
Okay, look, Ross. I do not want Emma going to the playground.
因为…
Because?
好吧 如果你真的想知道 我有心理创伤…
All right, if you must know, I had a traumatic...
我小时候曾经有过秋千意外
...swing incident when I was little.
- 真的吗？ - 是的 我当时四岁
- Seriously?     - Yes. I was 4 years old.
我坐在秋千上
And I was on the swing...
接着突然间我的头发被链条缠住了
...and then all of a sudden my hair got tangled in the chain.
为了要把我救下来 我妈妈必须剪掉一大撮我的头发
And to get me out, my mom had to cut a big chunk of my hair.
头发两边不对称了好几个礼拜
And it was uneven for weeks.
你竟然得承受那种痛苦？
And you made it through that?
我真不知道在电影里 谁可以扮演你的角色
I wonder who's gonna play you in the movie.
好 随便 你可以取笑我 我不希望艾玛去游乐场
Okay, fine, you can make fun of me. I do not want Emma going there.
而且我觉得克莱儿丹妮丝应该适合
And I was thinking Claire Danes.
听到你的悲剧 我深感抱歉
Look, I'm sorry to hear about your tragedy.
但是秋千非常地安全 此外 艾玛很喜欢荡秋千
Okay? But the swings are perfectly safe. And besides, Emma loves them.
- 你和我们一起去 你就会明白   - 秋千的时速大概一小时四十哩
- You should come, and you'll see.     - Those things go, like, 40 miles an hour.
而且当你荡到顶端时
And there's that moment when you're at the top...
你不知道是否能够重返地球
...when you just don't know if you're gonna return back to Earth.
太空中充满烧轨道运行的孩童
Space is filled with orbiting children.
拜托和我们一起去
Look, please, just come on.
当你看到艾玛的小脸蛋 我发誓 你不会后悔的
When you see the look on Emma's face, I swear, you won't regret it.
- 好吧   - 太好了
- All right.     - Good.
你不希望成为那种把无理性的恐惧
You don't wanna be a mothers...
加诸在小孩身上的妈妈
...who pass on their irrational fears to their children, do you?
"无理性"是吧
"Irrational," huh?
我会记得的 特别是 当你为了公寓里的蜘蛛大惊小怪时
I'll remember that next time you freak out about a spider in your apartment.
最好是能相提并论
Oh, yeah, that's the same.
我确定有三十种不同的有毒秋千
I'm sure there are 30 different species of poisonous swings.
我的天 审核领养的女士早到了
Oh, my God. The adoption lady is early.
好 来吧…
Okay. Okay. Here we go.
- 好   - 来吧
- Okay.     - Here we go.
抬头挺胸
Stand up straight.
面带笑容
Big smile.
嗨 这里是恐怖公寓吗？
Hello. Is this the Creepy residence?
我们在等审核领养的人 但你来得正好
We're waiting for the adoption lady. But, hey, I'm glad you're here.
今早打扫时 我发现了这个
I was cleaning this morning and I found this.
我不知道你想不想戴 但是…
I don't know if you wanna use it, but...
你真贴…
Oh, this is so sweet of you.
但是我不需要面纱 事实上 我不打算穿新娘礼服
Oh, but I won't be needing a veil. I actually won't be wearing a dress at all.
我告诉过你 我不会参加裸体婚礼
I told you, I am not coming to a naked wedding.
不是啦 我们不会举办大型喜宴
No, no, no. We're not having a big reception.
我们把结婚基金捐给
We took the wedding money we were gonna spend...
孩童慈善机构了
...and donated it to a children's charity.
太疯狂了
That's crazy!
抱歉 我没办法想像 把我唯一的结婚日像那样放弃
I'm sorry. I can't imagine giving up my one wedding day like that.
我们不一样 我不在乎举不举行大型派对
Yeah, well, we're different. I don't care about having a huge party.
这个才适合你 但是…
This is really nice for you, but...
拜托 我戴上这个 我看起来…
Oh, please. I put this on and, ugh, I just look like...
容光焕发
Well, radiant.
好吧 但谁在乎呢 我不需要漂亮的面纱或美丽的礼服
All right, but who cares? You know, I don't need a pretty veil and a fancy dress.
没错 你是许下承诺
That's right. You're making a commitment.
不管你在广场大饭店举行 还是…
And, you know, that's the same whether you do it at the Plaza or...
- 你们要在哪里结婚？ - 市政府
- Where you gonna do it?     - City Hall.
噢
Oh!
喔 听起来不错
Oh, that sounds nice.
我曾经去过那里当陪审团 他们把那里布置得很好
I was just there for jury duty. They've really spruced that place up.
好 没关系…我已经作了决定
Okay. No, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I've made my decision.
我真正想要的是一个盛大的婚礼
What I really want is a great big wedding.
呀
Yay!
- 但是你已经把钱捐给慈善机构了   - 我可以去要回来
- But you gave all the money to charity.     - Well, I'll just ask for it back.
- 我不认为你要得回来   - 为何不？
- I don't think you can do that.     - Why not?
这是她的结婚大喜之日 比那些笨小孩重要多了
This is her wedding day. That's way more important than some stupid kids.
真中听 宝贝 但别在审核领养女士面前漏了馅
That's sweet, honey, but save something for the adoption lady.
- 好 小心   - 知道
- All right, okay. Be careful.    -  Okay.
小心 小心她的头发…
Careful. Watch her hair. Watch her hair!
- 瑞秋 她只有三根头发   - 我知道…
- Rach, she's got, like, three hairs.     - I know. I know.
但是她的头发很漂亮 我的天 我拔掉了一根
But they're just so beautiful. Oh, my God, I just pulled one out.
我向你保证 她很安全 等着看她有多爱
I promise you she's safe, okay? Watch how much she loves this.
- 好…   - 甜心 准备好了吗 要荡了
- Okay. Okay.     - Are you ready, sweetie? Here we go.
好 小心
Okay, careful. Okay. Oh.
她在笑
She's smiling.
你看 她真的很喜欢
Look at that, she does like it.
- 看吧 我就说吧   - 噢
- See, I told you.     - Oh. Ah!
我的天 你看她 她是个小不怕死的
Oh, my God. Look at her, she's a little daredevil.
- 天啊 让我推 我可以推吗？ - 当然
- Oh, God. Let me push. Can I push?     - Oh, absolutely.
天啊 好 拿相机 在尿布袋里
Okay. Oh, God. Okay, get the camera. It's in the diaper bag.
好的
Okay.
你看？惧怕秋千 我打赌你一定觉得很傻
See? Scared of the swings. I bet you feel pretty silly. Aah!
我们真的要把钱要回来吗？
We're seriously asking for the money back?
那是结婚用的钱
It's for our wedding day.
这个家伙是不是同性恋？因为我们其中一人要使媚功
All right, now, is this guy gay or straight? Because one of us has to start flirting.
哇  你们要在同一天里捐第二笔钱吗？
Wow. You here to make another donation the same day?
我想这从来没发生过
I don't think that's ever happened before.
同性恋 上
Gay. Go.
我的天 我好喜欢你的衬衫
Oh, my God, I love your shirt.
我们稍早捐的钱 我们想要回来
The donation we made earlier? Um, well, we want it back.
什么？
Excuse me?
那笔钱是要办大型婚礼用的 我们之前不想办
See, okay, that money was for a big wedding we thought we didn't want.
结果发现我们想办
But it turns out we do.
所以你们要求我们退还 你们给孩童的捐款？
So you're asking us to refund your donation to the children?
是的
Yeah.
感觉真好
This feels really good.
我很抱歉 但是婚礼 对我真的很重要
Yeah, I'm sorry. I am. But this wedding's just really important to me.
不关我的事 何况 这或许是件好事
Hey, it's none of my business. Besides, this is probably a good thing.
我们已经用丰盛的食物 和温暖的衣服宠坏孩子们了
We've really been spoiling the children, what with all the food and warm clothing.
这么说不公平 一个人的婚礼是很重要的
That's not fair. A person's wedding is important.
对我尤其重要
And especially to me.
我没举行过毕业派对 也没去过毕业舞会
Okay, I didn't have a graduation party. And I didn't go to prom.
我的甜蜜十六岁 在轮胎场被追着跑
And I spent my sweet 16 being chased around a tire yard...
追我的是个精神病息者 口中念着…
...by an escaped mental patient who, in his own words, wanted to:
"无论如何杀了我"
"Kill me, or whatever."
所以我应该要有个真正的庆典
So I deserve a real celebration.
而且我才不会让一个 满身大汗的小男人使我觉得内疚
And I'm not gonna let some sweaty little man make me feel badly about it.
她不是在指你和我
She could've been talking about either one of us.
嗨 我是罗拉 我是来做领养面谈的
Hi, I'm Laura. I'm here for your adoption interview.
你好 我是摩妮卡 这位是钱德
Hi, I'm Monica. And this is Chandler.
- 请进   - 谢谢
- Hi. Thank you.     - Please come in.
- 你要不要喝点什么？ - 喝水好了
- Would you like something to drink?     - Water would be fine.
我们很高兴你来
We're so glad that you're here.
我们对展开审核程序感到兴奋
We're really excited about getting this process started.
因为我们很爱小孩 爱死他们了
Because we love kids. Love them to death.
不是真的要他们死 那只是比喻的说法
Well, not actually to death. That's just a figure of speech.
我们爱小孩的程度…
We love kids the appropriate amount...
在法律规定的范围内
...as allowed by law.
- 你们这里很不错   - 谢谢
- Your place is just lovely.     - Thank you.
是啊 这里有健康家庭的成觉
Yes, this building does have a wholesome, family feel to it.
我觉得我好像来过这里
I feel like I've been here before.
这栋公寓还有别的夫妇收养小孩吗？
Are any other couples in the building adopting?
你是说一楼的那对夫妻吗？
Is that that couple on the first floor?
我们应该比他们早领养到婴儿的
Because we should get a baby before them.
那个家伙曾想要卖毒品给我
That guy tried to sell me drugs.
但是除此之外 非常健康的公寓
But other than that, wholesome, wholesome building.
喔
Oh.
- 怎么了？ - 我想起来为何我记得这里了
- What?     - I just realized why I remember this place.
- 是吗 为什么？ - 没什么
- Really? What is it?     - Oh, it's nothing.
我和住在这栋公寓的一个家伙约会 结果不是很好
I went on a date with a guy who lived in this building. It didn't end very well.
该不会是乔伊崔比亚尼吧？
That wouldn't, by any chance, be Joey Tribbiani?
- 是的   - 除了他还有谁
- Yes!     - Of course it was.
我们度过一个美好夜晚 隔天早上 他答应要打给我 结果他没打
We had a great night. In the morning, he promised he'd call and he didn't.
那个王八羔子
Rat bastard!
- 你们不是他的朋友吧？ - 天啊 不是
- So you're not friends with him?     - Oh, God, no.
- 不…   - 不…绝不
- No, no, no.     - No. Nope.
- 不 不   - 不 不 不
- No, no, no.     - No, no, no. No.
绝不是
No.
抱歉 我不该提的
Well, I'm sorry I brought it up.
你们两位有谁打算要待在家里？
So are either one of you planning on staying at home?
有人在吗？ 里面有没有人预约大明星？
Hello? Anybody in there order a celebrity?
噢
Ow!
那是谁？
What was that?
那只是个在走廊闲荡的疯子
That's just some crazy guy who roams the halls here.
不过他对小孩很好
He's great with kids, though.
- 罗斯 我的天 你还好吧？ - 狗娘养的
- Ross. Oh, my God, are you okay?     - Son of a bitch!
放轻松 我又没说脏话
Oh, relax. I didn't say the F-word.
罗斯 我就说吧 秋千很邪恶
Ross, see, I told you! Those swings are evil!
对了 就是这个
All right. That is it.
这将是艾玛此生最后一次荡秋千
That's the last time Emma is getting on one of those things for her entire life.
不…拜托 不是秋千的错 是我的错
No, no, no. Okay, it wasn't the swing's fault. It was my fault.
多少也是那个小孩的错
And kind of that kid's fault.
他还在笑 真天真
Who is still laughing. Nice.
拜托 我们能不能 在有人受伤前离开这里？
Come on. Can we just get out of here before somebody else gets hurt?
不 等等 我有个好主意 我要你坐在秋千上…
No. Okay, okay. Wait. I have an idea. I want you to get on the swing...
然后你就会了解没什么好怕的
...and you'll see that there's nothing to be afraid of.
我知道你在打什么算盘了
I know what this is all about.
你一直以来都在嫉妒我的头发
You've always been jealous of my hair.
我想说你已经是个成人了 好吗？你应该克服你无谓的恐惧
I just think you're an adult, okay? And you should get over your silly fears.
- 好啦…我会试试   - 很好
- All right, fine. I'll do it.     - Good.
- 除非你手握蜘蛛   - 在哪？在哪？
- If you hold a spider.     - Where? Where?
除非你手握蜘蛛
If you hold a spider.
我知道
I know.
你们里面没事吧 是我 乔伊
Guys, is everything okay? It's me, Joey.
领养
Adoption!
怎么回事？
What's going on?
就如同我刚刚说的 那个疯狂的…
Oh, it's just like I said, that crazy...
伯特 在走廊游荡
...Bert, roaming the halls.
- 没事吧   - 继续游荡 伯特
- Guys?     - Keep on roaming, Bert!
我们今天不想要疯狂
We don't want any crazy today!
- 到底是怎么了？ - 我们稍后再谈 伯特 一切都没事
- What's going on?     - We'll talk later, Bert. Everything's fine!
听起来不太妙
Everything doesn't sound fine.
他自己在外面没事吧？
Is he all right out there by himself?
没事的 他有看护照顾 他的哥哥…
Oh, yeah. He has a caretaker. His older brother...
厄尼
...Ernie.
- 芝麻街的伯特和厄尼？ - 这不是说编就可以编出来的
- Bert and Ernie?     - You can't make this stuff up.
你从来没有告诉我 那个家伙 还有你的甜蜜十六岁
You never told me about that guy and your sweet 16.
- 很抱歉发生那种事   - 已经结束了
- I'm sorry about that.     - Oh, it ended okay.
我的一个朋友枪毙了他
One of my friends shot him.
至少你将会有一场像样的婚礼 那是你应得的
Well, at least you'll get a proper wedding. You really deserve that.
是 真的 没什么伴随着我成长
Yeah, I really do. You know, I had nothing growing up.
就像那些没有我的捐款的孩子一样
Just like the kids I took the money from.
不…我知道你想要做什么 不要逼我再回去那里
No. No, no. I see where this is going. Don't make me go back there.
听着 我不能用这笔钱来办婚礼 它已经被污染了
Look, I can't have a wedding with this money now. It's tainted.
好吧 我们把钱捐回去
Fine, we'll give the money back.
如果慈善机构的那个家伙 找我们麻烦…
If that guy at the charity gives us a hard time...
我朋友已经很久没有枪毙人了
...my friend hasn't shot anyone in a really long time.
我觉得这里看来是个 养育小孩的好环境
I must say this seems like a lovely environment to raise a child in.
你大可检查所有的家具底下…
You are welcome to look under any of the furniture...
因为…相信我 你绝不会发现 任何色情杂志或香烟在底下
...because, believe me, you won't find any porn or cigarettes under there.
在我们四处看看前 让我确认一下 我是否记下需要的内容
Before we look around, let me make sure I have everything I need up to here.
何不让我带你瞧瞧婴儿房
Why don't I show you the baby's room.
- 你在做什么？ - 你们不让我进来
- What are you doing?     - You wouldn't let me in.
- 我以为你们有难   - 我们好得很
- I thought you were in trouble.     - Well, we're not.
但是你叫我"伯特"
But you called me "Bert."
那是代表危险的暗号
That's our code word for danger.
- 我们没有暗号   - 没有吗？
- We don't have a code word.     - We don't?
我们该有个暗号
We really should.
从现在开始 "伯特"就是代表危险的暗号
From now on, "Bert" will be our code word for danger.
那就是婴儿房
So that was the baby's room.
- 再来我们应该看哪一间房呢   - 哪里都行 但是沙发后面不行
- Uh, what room should we see next?     - Any room that isn't behind this couch.
有人不懂他的笑话 但我觉得他很风趣
Some people don't get him, but I think he's really funny.
我一点都不喜欢那样
I did not care for that.
你得离开
You have to get out of here.
你和社福人员上过床 却从没打电话给她
You slept with our social worker and never called her back.
她到现在还在生气 所以不能让她看到你
She is still pissed, so she can't see you.
好…
Okay, okay.
- 又怎样了？ - 我忘了我的球棒
- What?     - I forgot my bat.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我最后一次告诉你 我们不想和你做朋友
And for the last time, we do not want to be friends with you!
而且我们也不想和你买球棒
And we don't wanna buy your bat!
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
伯特…
Bert. Bert. Bert. Bert.
- 你们是他的朋友吗？ - 我可以解释
- Are you friends with him?     - I can explain.
乔伊？
Joey?
好吧
All right. Okay. Uh...
对
Wow. Yeah...
你竟然有胆回到这里
You have got some nerve coming back here.
- 我不敢相信你竟然从没打给我   - 你说什么？
- I can't believe you never called me.     - Excuse me?
你大概不记得我的名字了 便告诉你 我叫乔伊
You probably don't even remember my name. It's Joey, by the way.
不用费事告诉我你的名字 因为我记得一清二楚 女士
And don't bother telling me yours, because I totally remember it, lady.
我等你的电话 等了好几个礼拜
I waited weeks for you to call me.
我给了你电话号码 你从没打给我
I gave you my number. You never called me.
别想转移话题
Don't try to turn this around on me.
我不是社会福利…
I am not some kind of social work...
可以让你…
...that you can just...
说做就做
...do.
- 我很确定给了你电话号码   - 是吗？拜托用脑想一想
- I'm pretty sure I gave you my number.     - Really? Think about it. Come on.
你是个漂亮的女人 既聪明又风趣
You're a beautiful woman. Smart, funny.
我们一起共度良宵
We had a really good time. Huh?
如果你给了我号码 为什么我会没打给你呢？
If I had your number, why wouldn't I call you?
我不知道
I don't know.
或许我搞错了 我很抱歉
Well, maybe I'm wrong. I'm sorry.
现在道歉已经太迟了 好吗？你伤了我的心
Hey, too late for apologies. Okay? You broke my heart.
你知道我得和多少女人上床 才能忘掉你吗？
You know how many women I had to sleep with to get over you?
- 乔伊 等等   - 不
- Joey, wait...     - No!
我等够久了 我不能再等了
I waited a long time! I can't wait anymore.
很抱歉让你们目睹这一切 我觉得很难为情
I'm sorry that you had to see that. I'm so embarrassed.
- 真的没关系   - 我们完全能了解
- Oh, that's really okay.     - Yeah. We totally understand.
- 约会不容易   - 哇 你们人真好
- Dating is hard.     - Boy, you people are nice.
我得对你们说…
And I've got to say...
我觉得你们会是很好的父母
...I think you're going to make excellent parents.
萝拉
Laura!
我们回来了
We're back.
你们要来拿走更多的钱吗？
Are you here to take more money?
因为我想你们要找的是提款机
Because I think what you're looking for is an ATM.
不…我们是来把钱捐出来的
No, no, we're here to give the money back.
是的 你知道为什么吗？ 为了小孩好
Yeah. Because you know what? It's all about the children.
虽然也是为了婚礼
Although it's also about the wedding.
好吧 拿去 天啊
Ugh. All right, here. No. Oh, God.
如果我还没有说的话 先生 恭喜你
If I haven't said so already, sir, congratulations.
好了 你知道吗？够了
Okay, look, enough, all right?
我得出面干涉 而且我的立场坚定
I'm stepping in and putting my foot down.
身为你未来的丈夫 我要为我们做决定
As your future husband, I'm gonna make this decision for us.
你觉得我们应该怎么做？
What do you think we should do?
- 已经不是你们可以决定的了   - 什么？
- It's not your decision anymore.     - What?
我代表纽约儿童保护协会 拒收你们的钱
On behalf of the children of New York, I reject your money.
- 但是我们要给你钱   - 我把它还给你们
- But we're giving you this.     - And I'm giving it back to you.
接受吧 当作是捐款
Come on. Consider it a contribution.
真是慷慨
Well, this is very generous.
拿着支票
Please, take the check.
举办一场盛大的婚礼 一起拥有美好的生活
Go have a great wedding and a wonderful life together.
听起来不错 我们可以存钱 几年后再回来这里
Sounds good to me. We can save up, come back...
捐一笔更大金额的款项   - 没错
...and make an even bigger donation.     - Absolutely.
当你们回来时 请找布莱恩
And when you do, ask for Brian.
- 是你吗？ - 不是
- Oh, is that you?     - No.
喂？
Hello?
喔 嗨
Oh, hi.
我的天 真的吗？ 我等不及要告诉钱德了
Oh, my God, really? I can't wait to tell Chandler.
好的 再见
Okay. Goodbye.
- 打错电话吗？ - 萝拉打来的
- Wrong number?     - That was Laura.
她帮我们写了一份很好的报告 我们正式列入等候名单了
She gave us a great report and we're officially on the waiting list.
- 太棒了   - 现在我们只要等电话…
- That's great.     - Now we just wait for a call...
会有人告诉我们 有婴儿等着我们带回家
...and someone tells us there's a baby waiting for us. Oh.
喂？
Hello?
你有看到乔伊的球棒吗？
Have you seen Joey's bat?
好了 我抓到蜘蛛了
Okay. I got a spider.
有两只 我选了大的那只
There were two, I picked the bigger one.
- 好吧   - 来吧
- Okay.     - Okay.
感觉非常正常
This feels perfectly normal.
好 该你荡秋千了
Okay, get on the swing.
好吧
Okay.
好
喔 好
Oh, okay.
哇哦
Wow. Whoa.
- 你看   - 我可以的
- See?     - All right. I can do this.
你看吧 我为你高兴
There you go. Good for you.
你知道吗 我已经习惯这个小家伙了
You know what? I'm getting used to this little guy.
- 我甚至感觉不到他在我手中了   - 那是因为他在你脖子上
- I don't even feel him in here anymore.     - That's because he's on your neck.
罗斯…
Whoa! Ross!